Hey. Hey. Hey.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Hey, Heat.
[Music]
down.
Hey, hey, hey.
[Music]
D.
Go on.
[Music]
D.
Black.
[Music]
going.
Hey
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Hey, heat. Hey, heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
Heat.
[Music]
Heat. Heat.
[Applause]
[Music]
Heat.
Hello.
[Music]
Hey there.
>> Hey there.
>> It's the program and I'm hearing my own
voice back in my headphones. Okay. No,
now I'm not. Now it's okay. Uh anyway,
I'm Ted R. That's John Kuryaku over
there. Uh thanks as always for joining
us here on drogram where we try to
deprogram you from all the corporate
mainstream propaganda that's in the
medium in the media and everywhere else.
It's like the old Palm Olive uh
commercial uh propaganda. You're soaking
in it. Um
>> that commercial.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm old. I remember that
stuff. Um all right. So today we're
going to talk about uh go the starvation
crisis in Gaza. Um the the prospect of
even more sanctions against Russia. I
guess they found some lying around
between the sofa cushions that they
hadn't used yet. Trump's visit to
Scotland. Uh there rumors that uh Jain
Maxwell, whose name I still can't
pronounce, uh could be pardoned by
Donald Trump. Um I still don't
understand why she would be. uh ice
raids here in New York City. Uh things
are going to get spicy here, I have a
feeling, this week. Uh and the a
ceasefire deal between uh Thailand and
Cambodia seems to have been at least in
part prompted by Trump's tariff threats,
which is one of the strangest uh
combinations of stories I've ever heard.
>> Yeah.
>> John, shall we just get into the
situation in Gaza?
>> Yeah. Two Israeli human rights
organizations today uh issued a joint
statement saying that the Israeli
government is committing genocide. They
use the word genocide for the very first
time.
>> Wow.
>> Now, the New York Times craps all over
this announcement by saying, "Well,
these are liberal groups in Israel and
they're frequently uh in opposition to
the Israeli uh the Israeli government."
But listen, genocide is genocide. And
they compare what the Israelis are doing
in Gaza to what the Germans did to them
in the Second World War, minus the
ovens. I think this is a very, very
important development. In the meantime,
the Israelis deny, deny, deny that there
is any such thing called genocide. They
say that they're fighting a war with
Hamas. Well, if you're fighting a war
with Hamas, why are so many children
starving to death? And if if you're not
committing genocide, then why would you
make this grand announcement today that
you're allowing you're allowing
shipments of food? If there wasn't a
starvation policy, you wouldn't need to
make an announcement that you're sending
in uh uh plane loads of food being
dropped uh on pallets and parachutes.
>> Not to mention a not to mention it's a
starvation policy that was announced
immediately after October 7th, 2023. and
uh and the by the very same people who
are still in the government and who
never retracted those statements or even
apologized for them. So, John, one of my
favorite comments that came out in the
last day was from uh everyone's uh
favorite prime minister, Benjamin
Netanyahu. He said that u in response to
the pressure, Gaza would receive minimal
humanitarian aid.
that where where we're at is that's an
up that's more than
>> I mean minimal.
>> Yes.
>> I mean
>> because there was no food, none. The
policy is to starve civilians.
>> It is.
>> It's to kill people.
>> And so I mean aside from the question of
you know how do you get up every morning
and live with yourself? Um I mean
there's the question of like the
messaging right? I mean, it's kind of
like that was greeted totally without
commentary by outfits like the New York
Times. Like, it's it's blasé. Like, no
big deal. I mean, as the occupying
power, Israel has a responsibility to
provide ample sustenance and food,
water, power, and everything else for
the people in the Gaza Strip. Uh and
they're like, "Well, we'll provide
minimal." Like even before even before
hostilities, Ted, there were five hours
a day of electricity and two hours a day
of water. That's all the Israelis
allowed.
>> And now even Donald, so you know, we of
course France has already decided to
acknowledge uh Palestine as a state. I
think that's a big deal. That
recognition is a huge deal. There's
pressure now on Kier Starber even in the
UK. Now, I think I've always thought
that the UK would be the second to last
to go and the US would be last.
>> So, I mean, the very fact that that
Starmer hasn't rejected this idea out of
hand, I think is massive.
>> Um, you know, John, those those those
two Israeli groups uh declaring that
this is genocide, that is a big deal. Of
course, and of course they're liberal
groups. It's going to start obviously uh
you know what you think Ben Gave is
going to call it genocide maybe
eventually we'll get there uh but right
now this is where how it starts I mean
it's it is a big deal I mean there's
definitely you know you can sense the
shift in in the you can just feel it
right I mean the ground is falling out
from under uh you know from support for
the uh far-right regime of Netanyahu
specifically and Israel in general.
You're absolutely right. Kirst Starmer
already has a reputation for being weak
and ineffective, not just as prime
minister, but as a leader of his own
Labor Party. So, if we expected
leadership from Kier Starmer, we're
likely to be disappointed. However, with
that said, you make an important point
and a correct point that I too would
have believed that the Brits would be
the next to the last country to to turn
away from the Israelis and in favor of
the Palestinians. I'm going to change
that now and I'm going to say that the
next to last country to turn away from
Israel will be Germany. The Germans are
irrational in their support of Israel,
as irrational as American policy is. and
they're going to be with the Israelis
until the bitter end.
>> And that's because of their history.
They feel like they they're they're the
ultimate uh guilty liberals.
>> That's right. That's what it is. They're
they're the guilty liberals. Like, oh,
look what we did. We have to make right.
So, we'll help the Israelis do it to the
Palestinians and that'll put us right
with the Israelis.
>> It's insane.
>> Stupid policy.
>> Yeah. No, I mean I mean of course
obviously look I could understand the
discomfort but I mean it's going to
become
we can see already like Hakee Jeff and
people like that. Um they're having to
backpedal. Um all these politicians they
were in the safe place, right? And that
was true in Germany too. It was always
safe to support Israel. You and I both
know John 10 years ago if you criticized
Israel you were in tremendous danger.
You were jeopardizing your your
reputation, your job. Um, you know, you
you know, you'd be accused of being
anti-Semitic. I know when I did
anti-Israel cartoons 30 years ago, I got
accused of being anti-Semitic. Um, so
nothing's, you know, but now
>> ridiculous.
>> It's safer.
>> It's safe.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> Thanks to those Thanks to those photos
that are coming out.
>> Photos. It's the photos that have done
it. And you know what's funny, too?
>> No one cares about starving and dying
adults, by the way.
>> No, it's the children. It's the
children. And for the first day or two
after those photos ran, there were a lot
of complaints in the UK that the BBC had
either doctorred the photos or took the
photos in other countries during famines
and said they were Palestinians. Now,
not true. These are legit photos taken
by BBC photographers of Palestinian
children.
>> Yeah, they are. And there and there's
tells, too. And but you know, look, it
it's look in in fairness, deep fakes are
a real thing. We've seen tons of photos
of like old disasters repurposed to uh
to present as something that's
contemporary outside of the Middle East
crisis. So, it's not like impossible
that such a thing would happen. But the
Israeli government, they have some
balls. The official spokesperson today
went on and said this is fake news. This
is fake. These photos are faked. There
is no famine in Gaza. This is the
official policy uh the official
statement of the of the government. Um
>> scandalous.
>> They're kidding, right? I mean, who did
they I mean, how much more full of [__]
could you be? And I mean, and I think
the denials only make their situation
worse. I mean I mean, the Israelis are
rightfully in a no-win situation, but
the only thing they could really say is,
you know, this whole Gaza Humanitarian
Fund Foundation thing didn't work out.
we're going to let the UN back in and uh
you know, let the chips fall where they
may. And and then there was that article
the in the over the weekend in the
Saturday New York Times media dump uh
where they revealed that actually um
everything that Israel said about Hamas
stealing aid was not true.
>> It's not true.
>> So they just they were just making [__]
up. Yeah. But it it you know it just
appear it appears like so the times
dutifully released it on the Saturday
but
>> when nobody's
>> well supposedly right but that's not
really true anymore. I don't think the
New York Times understands that. I think
like they they think nobody read it.
Actually Saturday is a major news day on
the internet now.
>> Good.
>> You know they're all old down there on
8th Avenue and 42nd Street. They're
they're they're very very old. not the
people who work for them, but the the
editors who make the call, they they
don't get it. And it's kind of great.
>> Donald Trump today said that there
should be more aid going into Gaza. He
was asked if the photos were faked. He
said they looked real to him.
>> Good. That that that's actually a major
announcement from from Donald Trump for
him to say something like that. But
then, you know, we look back to just
what was it, Ted? a week, maybe a week
and a half ago, when Benjamin Netanyahu
was in Washington and half the Senate
showed up to take a a selfie with him
with Cy Booker, who I briefly flirted
with the idea of supporting uh in a
presidential run, that's that's gone
from my head. Uh but but him like lamely
trying to hide his face like he was
having second thoughts just as they were
taking the picture.
It it enrages me. I can't believe that
this guy is not treated like a war
criminal. Well, yes, I can believe it.
It's the United States. And then we we
impose sanctions on the UN special uh
reperator for uh for uh torture. It's
just
I just can't believe it. Well, I mean,
if there's hope, it's that really I
mean, things really are changing. I
mean, uh, fast by the day. I mean, if
I'm the Israelis, I'm nervous as hell
right now.
>> Absolutely. Because there's no there's
no endgame for them. Um, they know what
they want to do. They want to kill every
Palestinian. The ones they can't kill,
um, throw out. But that's not a viable
policy. It's it's, you know, it's a
crime against humanity. You can't do
that.
>> There's a really great well-written
piece in Times of Israel, which is of
course, as you'd expect, a pro- uh
government, pro and very uh Zionist uh
publication, but basically it's saying
that the that it's claiming that Israel
has never had an articulated policy
throughout the conflict uh in terms of
war aims. And that's true.
>> That's true.
>> However, we know that there are war
aims.
>> Sure.
>> I mean, the and and Israeli generals,
they're not bad generals or tacticians,
right? No sir.
>> They I mean they they know what they're
doing.
>> There was a uh there's a minor Zionist
party that is a part of the uh Netanyahu
coalition and the head of this party
whom I had never heard of before said
yesterday, look the policy should be to
either kill or expel every Palestinian
and we shouldn't be afraid to say it.
It's like, well, you're the only one
who's not afraid to say it. It is a war
crime and a crime against humanity and
the legal definition of genocide. But
don't let me stop you from saying it.
>> It's also a violation of international
law for an official of a government to
even articulate such a statement. That's
right. He could be prosecuted for that
in the future.
>> Yes, he could. Yes, he could. Of course,
we would put sanctions on the court that
uh prosecuted him. So,
>> right. Yeah, of course. because it's the
judges you have to blame. Um, yeah. So,
how much So, I mean, okay, this is a
tough question. I don't It's probably
unanswerable. Uh, maybe we should both
try to answer it or just punt. What
happens next here? I mean, are we going
to How much longer is this going to go?
I mean, my feeling is Israel's got at
literally the amount of time that they
have before they cave in and let the UN
back in is measurable in days.
Seriously, I have to agree with you. Um,
there's pretty much nothing left to
destroy. All there is left to do is kill
as many people as you can kill. As we
said, that's not a viable policy. And
the only way that the Israelis can get
out of this is to turn back to the
United Nations, declare victory, declare
Hamas destroyed, and turn it over to the
UN. And then you can engage the Saudis
and ask them to join the Abraham
Accords, and you can negotiate some deal
later. But if the Israelis knew what was
good for them, they would declare
victory and go home.
>> They could offer Hamas's leadership um
exile, right? They could say, "That's a
good idea. We will let you leave.
>> Yes.
>> And you can go to a third country. I
don't know. To be determined. But and we
promise we will not send the MSAD after
you to assassinate you later on.
>> Right. Right. Nick has a good question
there. Uh Ted, uh what about the
American leaders of both parties who are
complicit in this genocide?
>> That's a you know, seriously, that is a
great question. Um it seems to me like
uh if you are the country that is the ma
the number one supporter I mean look I
guess it's it's a question what is the
role of the United States in this world
war II analogy right if Germany is
Israel then the United States is a close
ally like um it's an axis member like
fascist Italy or Imperial Japan or
perhaps Hungary or uh you know or
Romania any of those like fascist access
or um the collabor the Vichi regime in
France.
>> They were all prosecutable. They were
all um you know they were all legally
vulnerable. We focused on Germany at the
end of the war for obvious reasons. But
hey you know the leader of Vichi France
was condemned to death uh and then his
his uh sentence was then commuted to
life in prison because he was five
million years old. Um he was like 86.
>> Yeah. So, uh, you know, but I think,
yeah, no, I think I think honestly, um,
the political leaders of the United
certainly the president, certainly the
leaders of Congress, they should be held
to account legally for their role in
this. I mean, they they they set the
they sent the weapons, they sent the
money, they provided logistical support,
they provided intel. I mean, yeah, it's
people keep, you know, like John, one of
the one of the rules that like Zionists
who try to equate um criticism of Israel
with anti-semitism say is if it's
anti-semitism if you hold Israel to a
different standard than you hold other
countries. Okay? But the difference is,
okay, the when when uh Myanmar commits
um atrocities against the Rohingya
people, we're not paying for them or
sending weapons. It's it's horrible and
it's should be condemned and stopped,
>> but it's not really our thing. It's not
our responsibility, right? It's it's
everybody's business, but it's not
especi But Israel is the number one
recipient of foreign aid. It we run
interference for them in the UN Security
Council. We um you know, we provide them
with crazy amounts of intel and weapons.
Four billion dollars a year ever since
Camp David. And by the way, is it I
mean, if Jimmy Carter were here, I think
he would say like the reason that we're
bribing the Israelis and the Egyptians
with four billion dollars a year is to
say, "Cut the [__] and live in peace."
>> Well, they're kind of The Israelis broke
their part of the bargain. The Egyptians
didn't.
>> That's right. The Jordanians didn't.
>> No, everyone's Everyone's doing what
they're supposed to do, but Israelis
just do whatever the [__] they feel
like. I mean really it's part of their
like national personality if you believe
this is a thing.
>> It is. It is. That's absolutely true.
And you you absorb that as you walk
around um Tel Aviv or or Jerusalem or
anywhere else in Israel. You just you
can feel the vibe that people emit as
you're over there walking around. Every
Israeli that I ever knew
that that's not true. Mo almost every
Israelis, every Israeli that I ever knew
wanted to utterly destroy the
Palestinians, kill them all or exile
them all and let the Israelis live
happily ever after. Almost every Israeli
I know, even my American friends who are
Jewish and who consider themselves to be
Zionist. There's one guy who I've been
close to for for 20 years and I'm just
about ready to unfriend him on Facebook
because I just can't take his Zionist
propaganda anymore. And then he starts
off every post by saying um if there's
any uh anti-semitism, you are
permanently blocked. Well, any criticism
of Netanyahu to him is anti-semitism.
>> Ridiculous.
And I mean,
>> I I mean, I try not to do that because I
like to keep I like to keep lines of
communication open, but sometimes
>> there's really no choice because it like
makes you literally insane. Um, yeah.
So, I mean, we're
it's just, you know, I look, I got to
agree with you about the Israelis that
I've met, too. I knew one or two who
were very compassionate to the plight of
the Palestinians, viewed them as human
beings, believed that we needed to that
the Israelis needed to live side by side
in peace and friendship and harmony with
them.
>> But very that's really exceptional,
right? That most of them really view
them as rats and vermin. Um they to be
exterminated just like it is like what
the you know like that old joke like you
know what is Iraq doing on top of our
our oil? It's like it's like what are
these [__] Palestinians doing like
infesting our land? Like why are they
here?
>> Our holy land.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um you know, honestly, the only
people who are really the only the only
the only Jews who I know who are really
great on this in the United States are
people associated with um Jewish Voices
for Peace or Code Pink or any of the
other myriad of of uh
>> and those are big groups actually. and
they're big groups and they're
increasingly vocal and I think it's
absolutely wonderful.
>> Miko Pel is doing yman's work at as the
head of Palestine House here in
Washington DC. Um it just opened a
couple of weeks ago and it's it's small
but my goodness it's a start.
>> What is Palestine House? It is a meeting
space slashg gallallery
for um pro Palestinian human rights
groups, Palestinian artists, Palestinian
musicians. They have programming there
several nights a week. It's up on
Capitol Hill and one of the one of the
city's big property developers who
happens to be Lebanese American uh
donated the building and uh and they
have a small endowment. So they're
they're able to uh they're able to make
a go of it. And Yellow Banana, even
Tucker Carlson sounds sane to me now. Oh
my god. I can't tell you how many times
I've had that conversation with friends
just in the last two weeks. Like
>> Tucker has changed, too.
>> He's changed. He's He's
>> He'll be the first to say so.
>> Yes. Oh, thank you, Dana. Um Tucker once
he was free of the bonds of Fox News was
was able to be himself, his libertarian
self. And while he's still completely
wrong, for example, on the issue of
abortion, I love the guy. I consider him
to be a friend, a loyal friend, and he's
100% right on Palestine,
and we should join forces. You know, I I
take a lot of heat about this, too, and
I know you do as well, Ted, but but
parties be damned in our country. We
should join forces with everyone who
agrees with us. We can get so much more
done than if we impose these ideological
purity tests that do nothing but divide
us. I feel really strongly about that.
>> No, I totally agree. You know, I I I
think about the I I know a lot about the
French resistance, you know, in the
during when the Nazis invaded France.
monarchists fought alongside communists
and socialists. It was like the idea was
like we have an infestation here of of
of Nazis. We can't like be worrying
about each other. We we'll f my my
favorite example of this was um uh uh
what was his name? The leader Shamasud,
the leader of the alliance Shamasud. Did
you ever meet him by the way?
>> Once right before right right before he
was assassinated.
>> Yeah, that was on uh 910 right when that
happened.
>> Sure was. So um so Akmed Sumasid was the
a legendary general from the Pangier
Valley um Taji northern from the
northern alliance and he unified um the
anti-Taliban the antis-siet resistance
right and he famously convened all these
tribes and factions who all hated each
other and they all got together and he
held up a a cup a cup of tea toasted
everyone and said first we kill the
Russians then we kill each other and
remembering that
>> that remembering that order is very very
important. Uh right now we we have a you
know we have a major problem. I mean on
a foreign policy front um we're kneedeep
in militarism, adventurism and zionism
and complicity with genocide. We've got
whoever everyone who's against that left
right whatever we got to get together.
Here in the United States, we have, you
know, rampant billionaires and
corporations underpaying everyone,
screwing us all, taking away our health
care, left, right, middle. Everybody's
got to like fight for ordinary people. I
mean, we've got to get together. I mean,
there is a there's a place to unify
between the left and the the populist
left and the populist right. For sure. I
mean, the populist right has been
betrayed by Trump and they know it.
>> Yeah, that's absolutely true. Uh Reed
makes a couple of uh of good points here
too. Tucker's not going to cross the
Rubicon because this kid actually does
work for things. That that is that is
true. Um and it's not just Palestine
that he's right on. He's also talking
about Zionist manipulation in the United
States. He and I had a long conversation
about that actually about um Israeli uh
intelligence operations in uh in the
United States and how the Israelis for
decades now have been spread out all
over the country trying to infiltrate
our defense contractors and steal our
defense secrets because we only give
them 95% of what we have. They want the
other 5% that uh
>> that's the Israeli way. Yeah, it's the
Israeli way. Yasutaki,
thank you for joining us.
>> All right.
All right. Are we deprogrammed on Gaza
right now?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm all fired up about Gaza.
>> There will be. Oh, me too. Um, and by
the way, seriously, for people who are
coming to this point of view belatedly,
welcome.
>> Welcome. And and thank you. And uh
better late than never and we're not
going to give you [__] Uh,
but seriously, uh, welcome aboard. We
have to put an end to this [__] And if
it, you know, look, we all have been
propagandized. So, it's not shocking
that it takes some people longer to be
depropagandized than others. All right.
So, Russia,
um, Donald Trump had set a 50-day
deadline, which some people had
interpreted as basically like a a wink
wink nudge nudge to President Putin,
like you guys can do some mopping up
operations there uh in preparation for a
ceasefire negotiation. But I'm really
looking for you after 50 days to sit
down with the Yukis and sit down and
work out some
>> preoperative phrase being after 50 days.
>> After 50 days. Well, um this is kind of
like one of those things like um I had a
credit card where they used to say you
had 28 days to pay and then like one day
I got a late notice after I paid 10 days
afterwards and it was like but I thought
and they oh yeah we changed that you
didn't read that like 5,000word thing
that we that we sent you. Uh yeah, so
that's kind of like what happened to
Russia. I mean Putin just got his notice
like oh no um 50 days has been revoked
now is to now is now I am in
>> it might be 10 to 12 days maybe
>> maybe so okay so then Trump saying if
the Russians don't hop to it and make
peace with Ukraine and the Ukrainians do
appear more willing to to talk and get
serious than ever before but who knows
with them. Um, okay. So, what exactly is
the threat here to Russia? I don't
really get it because they've already
slammed them with sanctions. They got
you and me fired. I mean, it's like what
more do they I mean, what more could
Trump do? I know we still buy [__]
particularly energy from Russia, but you
know, the Russians can they have other
they have other markets. It's oil, you
know. It's like I used to work in
banking and we used to say you know we
have the one product everyone wants
money and it's like well when you sell
oil you have you have another product
everyone wants. I mean
if you're Putin are you losing any
sleep?
>> No because the Indians and the Chinese
have said whatever oil you have we'll
buy it. And after that initial shock,
you remember right after the Ukraine
invasion, um Sergey Lavrov, the Russian
foreign minister said that that the
Russians were surprised at the quickness
with which the US was able to impose
sanctions and we kind of knocked them
off kilter for three or four weeks and
then they realized they don't really
need the United States, including the
American banking system. when they can
turn to the Indians and the Chinese and
everybody else in the world that doesn't
want to fall into line behind US
sanctions, they realized they're
actually not having too tough of a of a
problem with it.
>> Well, not to mention it terrorized the
rest of the world, right? Like, you
know, President Xi and uh and uh and
Prime Minister Modi of India, they
looked at that move and they said the
[__] the [__] Americans are
they're feckless and reckless, right?
They will kick anyone out of the
monetary system. You know, Brett and
Woods be damned. They don't care.
They're gonna do they they're going to
politicize the US dollar and the reserve
currency. We better get our own deal
going.
>> That's right. And just wait until the
BRICS countries make their own unified
currency. It's going to be it's going to
be a major change in global. It's an
atomic bomb.
>> That's right.
>> I mean, it could really like tilt the US
into a depression within days.
>> That's right. It really could. So the
Ukrainians, you know, finally saw the
writing on the wall with with Donald
Trump and the Russians saw an
opportunity that, you know, hadn't been
there before. And so they're not afraid
of sanctions. We can sanction them from
now until kingdom come. They don't care
about the sanctions because they don't
need us, right?
>> It's really as simple as that.
>> So I mean, obviously that said, in a
way, Trump's in a little bit Trump is
pushing on an open door, right? I mean,
Russia doesn't want this to go on
forever. They're not stupid. It costs
money and time and they're not really
getting anywhere. I mean, the lines
aren't moving very fast. I mean, pretty
much this is, you know, it is what it
is. You look at a map of where the front
lines are. This is where it is. And you
might have some land swaps to make
things a little more even so we don't
end up with a Thai Cambodian situation,
but it is what it is. And I and I know
Putin gets that. I mean, so
>> like so I guess the question is
is peace is a ceasefire is a deal
possible this year.
>> Yeah, sure. Sure. But there has to be
something really special in it for the
Russians because they're just not
feeling under any pressure.
>> Yeah. They're just not
>> I mean certainly an end to all the
sanctions would be a start, right? But
then I think reintegration I you know
honestly I bet G8 membership would be
just the tasty treat that Putin would
like.
>> I would agree with that.
>> I would agree. Remember the the G
>> and Donald Trump has said it should be
the G.
>> Do you remember the G7 plus one?
>> That just that was offensive. That was
offensive and it was
>> that was like Gilligans Island and
Russia and the And the rest.
>> Yeah. and all the rest here on Billy
Gins.
>> Yeah. You know, they by the way, I don't
know if you know that, right? The rest
were the professor and Maryanne
>> and they changed it in season
>> and they and they Yeah, they negotiated
a deal and uh Maryanne's the only one
who any made any ever made any money
from that show. Um she her agent
negotiated like some insane deal for
residuals and syndication back then.
They were like, "Syndication? What's
that?" And she like lived in total
luxury the rest of her life.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, she did.
>> Russia though, I mean, so do you think
so? That might be enough, right, to
bring to get it done with Russia, but
then are the you know, can can Trump
lean on the Ukrainians and force them to
sign a deal? I mean, he can, but he's
getting pressure from the militarist
forces and the supporters of Ukraine
politically breathing, you know, he's
got Lindsey Graham and people like that
breathing down his neck. So, which way,
how does Trump fall on this? He has to
do I want my Nobel Peace Prize, right?
Or do I want to suck up to Lindsey
Graham? Like, what is it? I think he
wants the Nobel Peace Prize, which is
why
uh he called the Cambodians and the ties
over the weekend and told him to cut it
out and now they announced a ceasefire.
>> Yeah, let's just let's just skip to
that. Let's talk to that. Let's talk
about that because I I thought it was an
interesting story. Right. So, back in
1907, French the French uh they they
they they were the colonial power.
Thailand was independent, right? Um but
uh Cambodia was a French colony and they
signed a a a uh border deal. They
declared they defined the border mostly
along a river but with an exception and
the the way that the treaty look the
text of the treaty basically put these
temples inside of Thailand and uh in and
then but the map that accompanied it put
the temples inside Cambodia. Um, so
Cambodians are like, "We're going with
the picture." And the ties are like,
"We're going with the words. I love this
whole thing." And so they've been like
at it for years over this, although most
of for most of the time, no one cares.
Uh, basically for five days there's been
fighting across the border with heavy
artillery. So, and and some F-16 action.
Um, the ties that we as we talked about
last week obviously have the military
advantage overwhelmingly.
And basically over the weekend, Trump
said, "We have an August 1st deadline
for for all of the tariffs with every
country on Earth. And if you two rascals
don't cut the [__] you guys will get
like hit by massive sanctions. I mean,
by massive tariffs and bring it to an
end now." So Thailand, I get they have a
lot of trade with the US.
>> Yes.
>> Cambodians don't have [__]
>> No, they have they still
>> Yeah.
So, so I think with the Cambodians, they
just want it to be over because they're
getting their asses kicked, right?
>> Agreed.
>> Okay, that was my take. So, the ties
wanted to be over. The ties are
motivated by But who ever heard of
ending a Who ever heard of ending a a
war with a threat of tariffs?
>> I mean, it's kind of brilliant.
>> It is brilliant, actually. And it and
it's worked. I mean, listen, this whole
tariff thing you and I both said was
nuts when it was first announced he was
going to crash the international economy
and son of gun if it if it's not working
out.
>> It's true,
>> you know. Yeah.
Yeah.
Sorry, Jay. We've been talking about
other things. But anyway, tying this
back in the past, I'm sure it'll come up
again. Tying this back to um Ukraine and
uh and Russia, uh somebody pointed out
that, you know, the Pentagon has this
plan going into 2026. Of course, it
does. That's what the Pentagon does. It
does near, medium, and long-term
planning. Um
>> Oh, yeah. They have plans to invade
Likenstein.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They're called
off-the-shelf plans. They come up with
the plan to invade XYZ country, and they
just put it on the shelf, and someday if
you need to invade that country, you
pull it off the shelf, and you do the
invasion. case of emergency, please
break glass.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's right. So, um
I think that the Ukrainians are
exhausted. I think that they don't fully
trust Donald Trump to keep funding them
and sending weapons. And they also
realize they're going to have to concede
some territory at least to the Russians.
But the Russians I I don't understand
what the motivation is to keep fighting
unless the Russians are serious about
overthrowing uh Zalinski,
taking you know Odessa someday.
Who knows?
>> Otherwise if they are it's not acting
rationally because I mean Russia has
been kind of fighting with one hand tied
behind their back. Yeah, I mean they
have not committed the full weight of
the Russian military to this project.
They've treated the Russia Ukrainian war
as kind of like an important project,
but one of many, not like an existential
uh, you know, fight for the Russian
Federation. Um, this is not total war
for them. It's like something they're
just doing doing on the side kind of.
And that's why they're not I mean if
they threw everything they had at the
Ukrainians they would overthrow Zalinsky
and overrun the entire
>> Absolutely. Absolutely.
>> So what's going on?
>> I don't know. I'm I'm wondering if
they're trying to put so much pressure
on Zalinski
that the Ukrainians rise up and push
Zilinski out. let Zilinsky take his
money and run to London and then they
might be willing to sit down and
negotiate a settlement with whomever
steps in it fills the void. I don't
know. I don't know. Otherwise, the
Russian position over the last several
weeks does not make sense to me.
>> Yeah. Old Cold War thing about a, you
know, a mystery wrapped in an enigma.
>> That's right.
>> Yeah.
>> A riddle wrapped in a mystery wrapped in
>> That's right. Russians are hard to
figure out sometimes and sometimes and
yet they're also the most
straightforward people in the world
sometimes too.
>> Yeah, sometimes they are. Um, no, yellow
banana. That's that's one of the issues.
The the Ukrainian constitution
>> election.
>> Yeah, the Ukrainian constitution says
that in a time of war, elections can be
postponed indefinitely.
>> If he zilinsky declared martial law and
then he said, well, under martial law,
you can't have an election. So, I would
love to have an election, but because of
the thing that I declared, we can't have
one.
>> Can't do it.
>> And there's no And there's no uh by the
way, the US had elections during the
Civil War. Just saying.
>> Yes. Yes, we did. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I think uh Pamela, I think that's
right. The Duran, you know, those guys
in the Duran, they know more about
Russia and more about the Russia Ukraine
war than I think anybody else on the
planet practically. They're they are
saying that the Russians want to
demilitarize Ukraine and they use that
term to denazify
the Ukrainian military. I think it's the
same thing. And um
>> so removing like the uh like the the far
right opponents like the Azafi type
people.
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> I don't know. I mean, it just seems like
it's like that's
Does Russia really want to micromanage
another country's military like that?
>> God forbid. I can't imagine.
>> Don't you have anything better to do?
>> Unless they push the Costa Rican uh
model where, you know, Costa Rica just
doesn't have a military. It just doesn't
exist. They have a national police
force, but there is no military. There's
no navy. They have a little coast guard
with, you know, one boat in the Atlantic
and one boat in the in the Pacific, but
that that's it.
>> Well, but the the West would never
tolerate that because Ukraine's a major
weapons purchaser.
>> It is. And a major weapons manufacturer.
>> What what what what weapons do they
make?
>> Oh, they are prolific. And with the 9
millimeter and the Kalashnikov, they
have factories just pumping them out.
Yeah.
>> So, this is a Soviet legacy.
>> Yes. Yes. Just like it is with the
Romanians.
>> Yeah, the Romanians make billions and
billions of 9 millimeter ammunition
every year.
>> That's that is super interesting. So
Cambodia and Thailand I I I would say
like okay, yes, it's fragile. It just
the the ceasefire just went into effect.
Like all ceasefires, this is one of
those we'll stop fighting now. Details
to be worked out later in terms of this
um you know 1907 uh border conflict. But
um my my feeling is that this is over
for now.
>> What do you think?
>> Yeah, I think so, too. Yeah, there's no
there's no upside to it.
>> Well, you could pick up some temples.
>> I guess you get the temples. Yeah, you
get the temples.
>> Who doesn't want their own Buddhist
temple? I'd take a Buddhist temple. They
look cool,
>> you know. Speaking speaking of Buddhist
temples, do you remember the the giant
Buddhas in central Afghanistan?
>> Yeah, in Bameyan. that in Bameyang that
the that the Taliban blew up like 1500
year old Buddhas. The Greek government
in the in the depths of its economic
depression tried to buy those Buddhas
just to save them.
>> Oh wow.
>> And with the intention of then donating
them back to a post Taliban Afghan
government.
>> Yeah. Then and Mulla Omar was like,
"Fuck you guys." Well, I remember like
Yeah. at the time. I mean, I think it's
important to remember that. Not to at
all um you know, I can't sign off on
what they did, but um you know, the the
the the rhetoric was really interesting
because it was 2000 and uh Mulla Omar,
the oneeyed leader of the Taliban at the
time, um said, "Look, you guys don't
care about our children who are starving
to death due to sanctions. So why on
earth should you care about the this big
sandstone thing? we're blowing it the
[__] up. And I remember thinking like,
man, that's brutal. ISIS had the same
mentality in Syria uh and and Palmira
and all that, but I could see it, you
know, like you you Westerners, you care
about this this 1500 year old thing, but
you don't care about people right here
and now.
>> Yeah. Isn't that the truth? First, I
want to thank USC and to to uh answer
his question. You know, my first couple
trips with the CIA, I went to little
teeny tiny piddling countries that
nobody would even pay any attention to.
And we would have these massive gigantic
American embassies that would take up
like an entire city block. And I
remember asking, I forget what country I
was in. It was like
Ethiopia maybe. And I was like, why why
do we have an embassy that's this
gigantic
in Ethiopia when we don't have any
national interest here? And um the
station chief told me um because we have
to make sure it's bigger than the
Russian embassy.
>> I mean, that's what it came down to.
>> So, it is the size of our national
penis.
>> That's exactly what it is. You go to any
African country and our embassies are
absolutely gigantic. And it's because
the Soviets had big embassies, so ours
had to be bigger.
>> It's not the size of your consular
representation. It's how you use it.
>> That's great.
>> So, uh, Reed S points out that a lot of
independent journalists and YouTubers
are visiting Afghanistan lately. I've
been watching them. I'm jealous. You
know, I I I love Afghanistan. I I think
it's honestly couldn't possibly. Right
now is the safest it's ever been in our
lifetime.
>> I'm absolutely sure that's true. I think
you could even go you could even travel
on the central highway. The highway is a
misnomer. Um but I bet you could do that
and be okay.
>> Oh, the the US embassy in Cairo. Oh my
god.
There there's a lot I probably shouldn't
say about the US Embassy in Cairo other
than yes, it's an enormous facility and
the Russian embassy is equally enormous.
It's ridiculous.
>> Reed has this question. Um, why is it
forbidden to take a photo outside the
embassy overseas? Not everywhere in
>> Well, I mean, it's it's they're not laws
that you can't take uh photos. They're
policy. Uh the the State Department's
Office of Diplomatic Security doesn't
allow photos, but because they can be
used to case the embassy. So, they have
people on the roof and they have people
looking at the the closed circuit TVs
and they'll uh they'll run out and grab
your camera. Yeah.
Yeah. Um, yes. Well, certainly I've been
to in a lot of former Soviet republics,
you can't take any pictures or in any
authoritarian state, you can't take any
pictures of any public buildings at all.
In Turk Menistan, I got into trouble
taking picture of a post office.
>> I got in trouble in in Saudi Arabia one
time taking a picture of of a sunset
that just happened to have the Ministry
of Interior off in the distance to the
to the left.
Did they try to take your camera?
>> They did.
>> Yeah.
>> And I I stood I stood my ground and it
was a standoff for a half an hour, but
they finally backed down when I pulled
out the black passport.
>> I bet they did.
>> Yeah, I bet they did.
>> And I genuinely was not I I don't care
what the interior ministry looks like. I
was genu genuinely taking a picture of
the of a desert sunset.
>> Yeah. No, I believe you. Um All right.
So, let's talk Should we talk about
Trump? He's in Scotland. Uh his mom,
>> yeah,
>> was uh born and raised in Scotland. Uh
>> yeah, but how incredibly rude is it and
what a gigantic violation of protocol
that he goes to Scotland and then
summons Kier Starmer to to fly to
Scotland to greet him.
>> It's It's like come here dog.
>> B and Starmer did. He got on a plane and
he went
crazy.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> So, yeah, it's interesting. Why do you
think there's so many uh people in
Scotland who are protesting him over
Epstein? I mean, he's got all people are
lined up along the side of the road
everywhere Trump goes, saying that uh
you know, calling him a pedophile and
saying that he's uh you know, need Why
do they care about the Epstein files?
>> I don't think they do. I think this is
just an easy swipe that they can take at
him. They protest him every time he goes
to his golf club in uh in Scotland. And
I think this is just this Epstein thing
has made it so easy to criticize him. I
mean, here we are weeks into it and
there is still zero white house strategy
with over how to deal with this. And
then today when he
>> Well, they played for time by by
shutting down Congress early.
>> That's exactly what it was. They played
for time by shutting down Congress until
September. Um but also
>> not gonna work.
>> No, it's not going to work. And and
>> just like the countdown at the front at
the beginning of our show, everyone's
just watching that countdown. They're
just waiting.
>> Yeah.
>> It's like this stupid statement that,
you know, are you going to pardon uh
Gain Maxwell? And he says, well, I have
the power to pardon Gain Maxwell. It's
like, oh my god. Like, have you learned
nothing over the last two weeks? That's
exactly what you shouldn't say in
response to a question.
>> Why not?
>> Because Gain Maxwell is a convicted
pedophile serving 20 years in prison.
His base is more anti-pedophile than any
other, you know, president uh presidency
in in American history. And what does he
gain by pardoning a convicted pedophile?
I think I know the answer to that
question, which is that it'll look like
he's being transparent. Um, I'm
pardoning her. Well, one of two things,
right? I I think he's like trying to
figure out what to do, right? But if he
pardons her, maybe he uh pardons her in
exchange for a gag order, like she
agrees to shut the [__] up, otherwise
she's going to have a a drone up her ass
one day. Um or uh and and and she it
also it fits in with his narrative,
right? There's nothing to see here.
There's nothing in the files. There was
no there was nothing in there.
Therefore, she never should have people
have asked she's never been should then
she should she she should never have
been convicted. Right. And it's like
yes, she never should have been
convicted. So it plays into that
narrative, right? It's like it keeps
your story straight as well. I mean,
it's a crooked story, but as straight as
you can possibly keep it. I think that's
that's what he's thinking.
>> That could be it. I would say his
thinking is incorrect, but uh but that
could very well be it. Yeah.
>> Bothers me very much.
>> Um well, I mean, and then the other the
other approach could be to say, "Hey,
I'll let her go." And that's part of my
transparency operation. Maybe she
doesn't have much to say, uh at least
not about me or anyone I care about
much. And that will show that I didn't
that we didn't have that we the
establishment have didn't have Jeffrey
killed and Maxwell
>> buried in in the buried in prison.
>> Like we're letting her run around. She
can go be on the view. Whatever she
wants to do and I'm going to show like I
didn't do anything wrong. I have nothing
to fear.
>> I think that's he's toying with those
two possibilities.
>> That's that's good thought. And he likes
to and another thing is he likes to blab
because it's I think it's part of his
test marketing. He likes to dip his toe
in the water. He raises the flag to see
if anyone salutes. Right? This is like
let's see how people react. If people
freak out and say like what the [__] are
you talking about? You can't pardon her.
Then it's like, you know, I never said
that. I would have never done that. Whi-
>> which is a very common thing that that
the White House does. I mean every every
president does this. you you release
this rumor just to see what the response
is going to be to the rumor. So it that
could be it. That could be it.
>> Let's I want to answer question.
>> That's a good question right there.
>> If they release the only person charged,
well, someone else was charged, too, but
he died. Um then where's the justice for
the victims? Well, that's the whole
point is then there's no vict there is
there are there were no victims really
um and the only person who is
responsible has died and because there
were no victims then we release the only
person charged.
I mean I don't believe in any of this
but
>> and and Trump mentioned Larry Summers
today. I missed that. That's
>> Larry Summers, former president of
Harvard, who thinks that women don't
know math.
>> Yeah. And former secretary of the
Treasury and and current
douchebag on top of mega douche.
>> Everybody who's ever met Larry Summers
says he's one of the most awful human
beings they've ever encountered.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've I have heard similar
things.
>> Well, I heard the other day that John
Kerry was somehow involved as well,
which doesn't surprise me one iota.
>> Really? No, no. Listen, I worked for
Carrie for two and a half years closely
closely with Carrie. Carrie's a scumbag
and he's a he's a fake progressive.
There's nothing like literally nothing
progressive about him at all. And then
he'll do just stupid [__] after stupid
[__] Like for example, I've been
working for him for a year and he bought
a yacht. And it wasn't just a yacht. It
was like an oceangoing ship, right? and
the the sales tax on it or not the sales
tax but the mooring tax on it was $6
million in um in Massachusetts. So he
registered it in in Rhode Island
um which doesn't have a moing tax. And
what he did he has, you know, he has a
big house on on Beacon Hill in Boston.
He's got a a giant ski lodge in um in
Idaho. He's got 120 acres in western
Pennsylvania. He's got houses all over.
a house in Georgetown. So he bought his
>> wife.
>> Well, no, he's got as much money as she
does.
>> Oh, is that true?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, he's
>> Hines is from the Hines Ketchup.
>> Yeah. John Hines's wife.
>> He's lovely, by the way.
>> Yeah. So, so Carrie bought this little
tiny condo in Rhode Island so he could
have a Rhode Island address and save $6
million by docking his oceangoing ship
there. And then there was this uprising
and even staff members, we went to the
chief of staff, really good guy who's
actually a member of the Kennedy family.
And um we said, "David, this is this is
a really bad look. You know, we're
supposed to represent him." And we're
out there and people are bashing us over
this over this failure to pay the
mooring tax. And eventually Carrie moved
the ship back to Massachusetts and paid
the six million.
>> So disappointing. Uh, do you want to
answer Reed's question?
>> I missed Reed's question. You got it
there.
>> Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh. Uh, what? Mr. Kuryaku,
why?
>> Oh, thank you. Oh, that's actually So,
so Reed, a couple of nights, a week, a
week or so before I left for prison, um,
I was at my wit's end trying to save
myself. So I wrote him an email to his
his private personal email address and I
said, well by then he was Secretary of
State. So I said, "Mr. Secretary, I'm
begging you to help me. Please ask the
president if he'll commute my sentence.
The the conviction would still stand,
but I could work and earn money for my
family and keep my family together and
put food on the table." and he waited
two three days and then he um he wrote
back and all the email said was please
do not ever attempt to contact me again
and that was the last time I heard from
him.
>> That is cold.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm sorry, John. That's brutal.
>> It was awful. It really was.
>> And no no explanation, no reason.
>> That was it. Please do not ever attempt
to contact me again.
>> Wow.
Uh, is Mike Baker a real ex CI agent?
You have a minute.
So, I replaced
>> We've got time.
>> I replaced Mike in Athens.
And, um, Mike's a good guy. He was a a
legit, you know, counterterrorism
case officer, operations officer. and um
he did something that was really really
like really stupid.
He and another colleague of ours were
doing surveillance on a terrorism
suspect
and you know the best security in the
world is probably old Greek ladies
peering through their their uh drapes
you know from their houses. And this old
Greek lady kept seeing these two men
sitting in a van day after day after
day. So she calls the cops and the cops
come and surround the van, right? Mike
and his and his pal can't get out.
>> Oops.
>> They finally open the door. The cops
pull Mike and the other guy out. And
inside the van, they have like three
different changes of disguise each. They
have like six different ID cards, all
from different countries and in
different names. And so they
used their get out of jail free card and
said call my boss in this certain
section of the embassy. They were
expelled from Greece. And then Mike
when Mike went back to headquarters he
was called into
into the director of counterterrorism
cent's office and Mike was kind of
bragging
to people that he was going to get an
operation for standing up to the Greeks
like that and instead they told him um
we want your resignation by the end of
the day and that was the end of Mike.
Yeah. I ended up working with his wife
uh for several years afterwards. But
yeah, Mike was the real deal. He just
made a really stupid mistake and uh and
he paid for it with his career. The
thing about Mike, too, you know, Mike
was a good-looking guy. I guess he's
still a good-looking guy. Um no, this is
well before cover.
He was a good-look guy. So, he went into
male modeling and he made a couple of
hundred, couple thousand bucks, you
know, modeling, whatever. And then he
tried to get his own show at Fox News
and it just didn't work. He ended up
pairing up with a KGB officer and
opening a security consulting firm in
London. I I remember they did um
security for Madonna's uh wedding to Guy
Richie. Uh but Mike never really made
money like I like he thought he was
going to and he never went back to the
agency.
>> Gotcha. John, let's talk about ICE. Um
it's uh in 4 minutes it'll be 6:00
Eastern time here in New York City. A
major protest is scheduled at that time
in City Hall Park in lower Manhattan. Um
ICE is bringing uh the big show from LA
to New York. U they're going to be
flooding the zone according to the
Department of Homeland Security. They're
bringing in their military hardware.
They're going to be grabbing and
snatching as many uh brownskinned people
as they possibly can.
>> The Washington Post told people, "Stay
out. Stay out of the area. It's going to
be hell."
>> Yep. And uh Yeah. And I have several
friends who are like, "Oh, should I tell
my friends uh to not go outside?" I'm
like, "Yeah, tell them to take the
couple take the week off from work, you
know." Um so it's going to be ugly.
It's, you know, most of this activity is
going to be happening out in the outer
burrows in Bronx, Queens, and Brooklyn.
um where they have a high much bigger
minority population. Um you know I'm
reminded of that quote from uh
Casablanca where um Humphrey Bogart
advises the Nazi major uh you know not
that probably not wouldn't be good to
invade certain neighborhoods in New
York. ICE is getting ready to invade
certain neighborhoods in New York. I
have a feeling they're going to find it
about as spicy as they found it out in
LA. The locals don't like it. We don't
like it here. And uh I mean I wouldn't
be surprised if uh there were clashes
this week.
>> The the New York Times said this
afternoon too that the that the level of
raids that are expected in New York will
dwarf the raids that we saw in Los
Angeles. Wow. This is this is big. This
is going to be very big and we should
probably expect to see some violence.
>> I would think so. Um, and you know, I
should remind people that here in New
York City, you know, due to the Supreme
Court ruling, this used to be a city
where it was illegal to own to own a
handgun unless you were a celebrity.
That's not true anymore. Um, you can
legally go out to, you know, Tennessee,
buy a gun, and bring it back. Hell, go
to Long Island and buy a gun.
>> People just cross the border into
Vermont and buy a gun.
>> It's it's it's really easy. Um, I'm not
encouraging it, but I mean I I I do
think it's it's likely likelier than
not. I mean I mean you I should point
out it's also been a long hot summer.
We're now in the fifth consecutive week
of over 90 temperatures. It's been a
non-stop heat wave with no end in sight.
Uh we have heat indices of over a 100red
degrees every single day. A my I've got
my AC going 247. Someone asked if I had
AC going for my cat. Yeah, but mainly
for me. Um, you know, it's but it's like
my cat's a Russian blue, so he doesn't
really like the hot weather. Um, but
it's it's definitely uh it's horrible.
So, and I and I think there's also going
to be a lot of resistance. There's
organized resistance here, you know,
advocates for uh for for and I think a
lot of non-immigrants, non-migrants will
help their migrant uh fellow New
Yorkers. I mean, I would.
>> It's against the law, but I would.
>> I would.
>> Yeah.
>> There's no choice.
>> Um, you morally I feel like I have to.
Um, John, did you hear about the case
about this 82year-old IRA IRA veteran?
>> Yes.
>> Oh my god. So, what the [__] So,
>> oh my god.
>> This dude is 82 years old. Um he was uh
convicted back in 1983
of trying to buy rockets to attack in
New York because you know in New York in
the 80s was a wild time. You could hang
out at Studio 54 and buy rockets to
attack the Brits. I'm sure it was
probably just a [__] the usual FBI
enttrapment sting operation. But anyway,
the point is he was trying to buy it. Um
he was the leader of the of this thing.
Um, and then the uh, Good Friday Accords
came and uh, as part of the Good Friday
Accords, all these charges were dropped.
He was released from prison. He was
given a green card, allowed to stay in
the United States.
>> Anyway, the Trump administration just
sent him a deportation notice. They
said, "You got to get the [__] out. The
dude's 82 years old, hasn't committed a
crime at all since 1983. Um, and uh,
he's got all sorts of heart problems and
he he's on Medicaid and everything else
you can imagine. and he needs that. I
mean, I guess Ireland has national
healthare. He'll be fine. But I mean,
they want to kick him back to Ireland
and he's like, "Fuck you. All right,
whatever." Um, but I mean, what's going
on, John? Is this just like, are these
letters being autogenerated for
everybody who's got a criminal record?
>> Well, they must be. They must be because
otherwise I don't understand the
strategy here. If you want to, you know,
raid all of the restaurants in New York
City and grab the the sue chefs and the
dishwashers, that's one thing. But if
you're if you're expelling, you know, a
Chilean torture victim, which was what
they did last week, and now an Irish,
you know, freedom fighter for all
intents and purposes,
>> then how who's making that decision? I
can't imagine that they're sitting
around a table, you know, some
conference room table in Washington with
a stack of files saying yes, no, yes, no
about who they expel. This has to be
computerenerated. There has to be like
this giant computerenerated list of
everybody who's ever been accused of a
crime and is here on a green card and
then they're being expelled. I I just I
otherwise I don't understand it.
Yeah. And and Houdini makes a point
there too. This way they can say, "Oh,
we're not just expelling brown people.
There have been white guys, too."
>> Yeah. Right. But I mean, 82 years old.
>> Yeah. 82 years old. Like, he's a real
threat to our society.
>> Yeah. Well, maybe, you know, they they
say it's like when they turn 83 is when
people get really crazy. Never know what
they might do.
>> Um, crazy.
>> Wow. So, I I don't know. Um, all right.
So, I guess we'll we'll we'll watch
that. We'll know more about it later in
the week when we have our We're here
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, 5:00 PM
Eastern. Um, and I'm trying to think, is
there anything else that we uh missed
here? Um, not really. Right. I mean, I
I'm a little scared.
>> Weekends are slow, but there was a lot
to talk about today being a Monday.
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> There's a lot. It's going to be It's
going to be a busy and very hot summer.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Always. So,
uh, let's see. Let's put Oh, let's put
let's put this up. This is kind of cool.
Um, thank you for the $10 donation. Much
appreciated.
>> Um, the German chancellor announced an
airbridge to Gaza today. What's an
airbridge?
>> But stress the importance of Germany's
friendship with Israel and the need to
remember October. Who could [__]
forget the October 7th attacks? People
just they don't start stop talking about
it. I mean,
>> an airbridge is a um it's a direct path
into another country's airspace where
you're guaranteed safety.
>> Okay. Okay. Like
>> Cypress to Gaza and the Israeli Air
Force won't shoot you down.
>> That's an airbridge,
>> right? What we need is a bridge. Bridge.
What we need is an open border.
>> That's right. I mean honestly
>> that's right.
>> All right. Well, I guess we are going to
declare ourselves sufficiently
deprogrammed for today.
>> Thanks everybody.
>> Thanks always for joining us. Much
appreciated. Uh please like, follow, and
share the show. Seriously, please do uh
if you're not already doing it. Um just
takes a second of your time and it
really makes a huge difference. Um, and
we really are are super moved by John
and I talk about this by the incredible
participation in the chats and just the
enthusiasm. You guys are amazing.
>> Love it. Thank you for these smart,
well-informed, relevant questions. It
really keeps things going. Thank you for
that.
>> Here, here. Um, and so, um, please, uh,
check us out here, uh, on our various
websites and stuff, but we'll see you
Wednesday, 5:00 p. a.m. Eastern time.
Same bat station, same bat time. Take
care. And if you're undocumented, get
documented. And if you can't get
documented, hide.